Your Majesty, watch out!
I was invited to have tea with the queen,
where we were shot at with arrows.
You are so super cool, Mimi! I adore you!
It would seem that the queen
didn't hate me after all.
SLAP
Well, well.
You're even more interesting
than expected, Mimi.
Always a Catch!
Knight Captain
Episode 4
How the One That Got Away Was Troubled
They're not getting away!
Secure the area!
Hurry!
The culprit fled outside the castle!
Don't let them escape!
My dearest Mimi!
Look after Her Majesty!
I'm glad, but...
The macarons the queen
recommended are ruined.
I wish I could punch the culprit
once for every treat they ruined.
Lady Maria!
We'll tidy up here.
Please head inside the castle.
His Highness must be worried about you.
Oh, really?
We'll call some knights.
But...
It's all right.
I can get there by myself!
Lady Maria!
She really is fast.
Is everyone all right?
Lord Raimondo!
We're terribly sorry.
Lady Maria left to see
His Highness by herself.
Even though she was just attacked?!
SHOCK
We're truly sorry!
I'll go find her. You handle things here.
Is this the right way?
Let's see... Huh?
I've never been here before.
Should I have turned right back there?
Mimi!
How do you do?
WHIFF
Huh? You evaded me.
How do you do, Lord Ireneo?
Goodbye, Lord Ireneo.
And then hello again.
You're no fun. We haven't
seen each other in ages.
This man...
Lord Ireneo of the Marchei family
is Prince Renato's cousin.
He's not His Highness's enemy,
but he is one to women.
He looks young, but
he's actually in his early 30s.
He must be quite the lady-killer
for Aida to say that.
I should be careful.
By the way,
I saw your feat of agility.
Thank you very much.
That was a compliment.
You really are interesting.
I've fallen for you all over again.
You always say that.
If you don't rein it in, His Highness
will be angry with you again.
Renato is so petty.
I'm not trying to take you from him.
Aw, shucks.
If only I'd met you first.
What?
You like me, don't you?
Yeah, right!
Right? I can tell.
Mimi, you can teleport?
Oh, please. You must be joking.
Lord Ireneo!
If you continue, I'll have to report
your behavior to His Highness.
Please stop this at once.
Ah, your escort has arrived.
Fine. I'll go.
Oh, Mimi, do you know about the bakery
that just opened in the royal capital?
Huh?
I hear their peach tarts are quite good.
We should go there on a date sometime.
I've been told not to follow strangers!
YUP
Lord Ireneo's fondness
for women is quite a problem.
I couldn't agree more, Lady Maria.
Listen, as the crown prince's fiancée,
you'll be approached
by all kinds of people.
Even at the royal castle,
be careful when you're alone.
Don't worry.
If anyone's too stubborn, I'll just give
them a little jab to the solar plexus.
What are you thinking? You can't do that.
WHAT
Honestly, you're not
without your own problems.
DRAG DRAG...
Then I sensed someone was there.
I kicked the table into the air,
and two arrows thudded into it.
Knight Captain
The queen's delicate shoulders
were trembling from the shock.
Where was the culprit?
I tried to find them,
but they were already gone.
Knight Captain
The colorful macarons flew through
the air and tragically fell on the lawn.
Oh, what a waste.
I've never seen His Highness
laugh like that.
And that's what happened.
What a splendidly powerful retelling.
You've still found no clues
relating to the culprit?
No, sir. We're still investigating.
We believe they were targeting the queen,
but progress is slow as there are
some puzzling elements.
Knight Captain
Keep looking into it.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, based on what I've heard
about your reflexes and agility...
I'd like you to join our chivalric order.
Hey.
You've questioned her enough, haven't you?
We won't give up!
Think it over!
I'm sorry everything's so hectic.
It's fine. I just hope I've been
useful to the investigation.
Mimi, I'm so glad you're all right.
Your Highness...
And again, thank you
for protecting my mother.
I didn't do anything.
I've said it before, but it's thanks to
the castle's tables being so sturdy.
Y-Your Highness!
I-I...
SQUISH
Are you sure you're not hurt?
I'm worried you might be injured
and simply haven't noticed.
Oh, please. You worry too much.
WHEW...
It's not safe. You should
stay at the castle tonight.
What? But I can't suddenly
impose on you like that.
The castle is prepared
to receive guests at any time.
And you're always welcome here.
But Your Highness...
Anyway, the angle of Mimi's
kick was perfect, too.
I see. Yes.
She is so, so cool.
Okay, okay.
Then she did this and that.
She's just so amazing...
According to the report I just received,
the queen hasn't calmed down yet.
Hey, Mimi!
And Lord Ireneo is
staying overnight as well.
It may be safer
for Lady Maria to go home.
I suppose you're right.
Anyway, what am I to do about Mother?
What?
You said you thought she hated you,
but she was fascinated by your
personality and martial arts skills.
BANG
She has trouble hiding her emotions,
and suppressing them
intensified her expression.
Oh, I see.
Please forgive her.
Of course. I'd like to be
on friendly terms with the queen as well.
Good.
Well, it's getting dark. I should go.
I...
I'm glad I got to see you twice today.
Mimi, perhaps you should
stay tonight after—
Prepare a carriage!
Assign more guards than usual!
Yes, sir!
Please don't sulk.
You're not officially engaged yet.
I know.
Raimondo, for Mimi's trip home...
Will she be taking that route?
Yes.
I'm concerned since that route has
seen a sudden uptick in bandit attacks,
but it's the only way
to reach the Kingdom of Muro.
But she was just attacked.
Being crown princess comes with danger.
I know, but still...
Perhaps Mimi would've stayed safe
if I hadn't proposed to her.
I can't help but think that.
I've instructed the Ametis family and the
academy to strengthen security as well.
Please rest assured.
I know.
I'll warn Lady Maria to avoid
sticking her nose into danger.
Be careful.
Security is tighter.
I feel kind of bad about it.
I shouldn't make Prince Renato
worry too much.
Always a Catch!
I'll fight off any assassins
no matter when they attack.
I must confirm my safety at all times.
This isn't quite strong enough
to serve as a shield.
Ms. Annovazzi?
Was I speaking out loud again?
I can't help but notice anytime
I sense someone looking at me.
Lady Rosalia's presence
in particular is easy to detect.
Well, look at you sitting over here.
I suppose a country bumpkin
would sit anywhere.
Lady Rosalia, have you
already finished your sketch?
Of course. We drew beautiful
flowers in the botanical garden.
Why don't you show her your drawing?
Take a look.
Wow, you're a great artist.
She's in the art club.
She's even won awards at contests.
Lady Rosalia, let me see yours, too.
Y-You don't have to see mine.
Never mind that. Show me yours.
But I'm not finished yet.
Let me see.
I-Is this perhaps avant-garde art?
Looking at that drawing filled me
with an unspeakable dread.
Let's go, you two.
You'll pay for this, Maria Annovazzi.
Lady Rosalia!
Lady Rosalia got my name right.
Uh, what are you doing?
Hey. Did I surprise you?
Lord Ireneo's presence
is even easier to detect.
Not at all. In fact, you
couldn't be worse at hiding.
What are you doing at
the academy, anyway?
I thought I'd tour the school
since I'm here.
I'm an alumnus, you know.
Yeah, right. You're here for
the young women, aren't you?
Don't worry. I'm currently only
interested in you, my dearest Mimi.
Did you draw this?
Yes, I did.
How novel. Art always starts with novelty.
What?
It's neither Baroque nor Neoclassical.
Yes, you're a truly interesting girl.
Lord Ireneo, you like
drawings and paintings?
Yes.
I know. We should visit
the art museum together.
What is it?
Oh, nothing. You looked like
my younger brother Teo just now.
What? I'm like your younger brother?
Does that mean I'm cute?
Yes, Teo is very cute.
Lord Ireneo!
Ah, what a shame. I must head back.
See you later, my dearest Mimi.
I see.
After class, you met the queen
and Lady Aida for tea,
then trained in the afternoon.
Your days are quite busy.
Since you're so busy,
you can't help falling asleep
while I'm speaking to you.
Did you really expect me to say that?!
I-I'm sorry!
I promise I'll listen next time.
Forgive me.
I appreciate you assigning more guards
to me, but I've been so tense recently.
Unbelievable.
This is important. Please listen closely.
Recently, the mountain
road to the Kingdom of Muro
has become dangerous
due to bandit attacks...
Hngh!
Lady Maria!
You're leaving tomorrow, you know!
Your movements are as beautiful as ever.
Your Highness.
Which forms would you like to see today?
The 30s, I think.
Very well.
30!
31, 32, 33!
34, 35!
36, 37!
38!
These blew all the way over here.
Number 38 was particularly impressive.
I know. That form is
one of my favorites, too.
SMILE
The key is to firmly plant your
feet and raise your right heel
as your center of gravity shifts
from your right foot to your left.
Also...
Calm down, Mimi.
I'm just glad you're interested
in my family's martial arts.
I can't help myself.
Come to think of it, you haven't
shown me the 40s or 60s yet.
I know. I can't show
those, not even to you.
They're family secrets.
Even within my family, only
my father and I know them.
SMUG
What? So only two people
in the world have learned them?
There's such depth to martial arts.
BLUSH
Why don't you take a break?
You seem to be working hard every day.
Are you getting enough sleep?
Did Lord Raimondo say something?
Do you know I fell asleep?
No. You're already so busy,
but you train every morning.
I just thought that must be difficult.
You don't need to worry about that
because the Annovazzis are
a renowned family of martial artists
who have served as Muro
royal guards for generations.
As heir, I received the same training
a boy would since I was a child.
You as a child...
You must've been quite lively and cute.
Not at all.
I was often mistaken for a boy
since I was so energetic.
Back then, I loved any
and all kinds of exercise.
I devoted myself to training.
But one day...
Mimi!
Are you all right?
Dad...
The lesson I learned was...
The Annovazzi family's martial arts
are for protecting those dear to you.
To protect those dear to me.
There's nothing I won't
do to achieve that.
I still feel that way even though
I'm no longer the heir.
So my morning practice, exercises,
and training are no burden at all.
So you get your strength
from your father.
Yes, but...
F-Fantastic! I have an heir!
Ever since Teo was born...
Dad's been reserved towards me.
All right! Let's go train, Mimi!
Wait, no.
Teo, M-Mimi has flower practice... right?
Things are a bit awkward.
Not that it bothers me at all.
I'm sure you'll be able to speak to him
like you did before again.
It's encouraging to hear you say that.
I'm glad.
Anyway, I'll miss you.
Y-Your Highness, I'm sweaty.
It'll get on your clothes.
I don't care.
I'll be back soon.
I'm only staying for one night.
But it takes six days
to travel there and back.
That's true.
I'm worried you might be
attacked while I'm gone.
SERIOUS
Normally it's the other way around.
Please be careful.
I appreciate your concern.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything reckless.
I'll be fine. I'm sure it'll work out.
When you say that, I can believe it.
SQUISH
I feel relieved. Thank you.
I'm sorry I can't see you off.
Give my regards to
Lady Aida and her family.
The prince is cute when he smiles.
He should smile in front
of the others more.
Is that all your luggage?
Yes.
I'll be borrowing your carriage, Uncle.
Sure. Say hello to your father for me.
It's about two days
to the border, isn't it?
Yes. My family's carriage
is coming to pick me up.
We'll meet at a nearby village,
and from there,
I'll travel for another day...
The Kingdom of Muro is so far.
I'm used to it.
Be careful, Mimi.
See you later.
Thank you, Aida.
Don't attract too much attention.
Okay.
Yah!
I'll be back!
I'll be back, Your Highness.
Translation: Sho Stifler
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Alicia Ashby
Quality Control: Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control: Michelle Tymon
STOMP
People say I speak my mind, but
maybe it's because I like singing.
I like bright songs that cheer you up.
Songs about fishermen catching
huge tuna are the best.
Next Time
How the One That Got Away Visited Home
The other day, I actually...
Oh, I spoke my mind again!